<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on A Hugo website</title>
    <link>/IndyUserWebpg/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on A Hugo website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/IndyUserWebpg/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Discussion of 2019 Plans</title>
      <link>/IndyUserWebpg/2019/01/15/jan2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/IndyUserWebpg/2019/01/15/jan2019/</guid>
      <description>We discussed plans for 2019. We had sent a survey to the folks in IndyUseR meetup group (~400 members). We got only 13 responses. We reviewed the responses and factored those into our discussions. The summary of the 13 responses are in this location.
We discussed the following:
 Have zoom meetings for the meetups so that folks can join online and location is less of a barrier Try to have meeting topics confirmed well before the meetup date Talked about having intro level talks to make the group welcoming to new R users Talked about bringing back R trivia segment for each of the meetups Will look into a R Training day  Topics of Interest: Some of the topics of interest listed in this year’s survey and talked about last year are listed in this location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learnings from EARL Conference - Derrick Kearney and Roy Budhaditya</title>
      <link>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/11/20/nov2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/11/20/nov2018/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Derrick and Roy shared their learnings from the recent EARL conference that they attended.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An introduction to the US Federal Budget with R by Stephen</title>
      <link>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/10/16/oct2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/10/16/oct2018/</guid>
      <description>Abstract The budget of the United States Federal Government is often a contentious issue. This presentation will provide a ‘rough’ introduction, covering where to get the data, provide a breakdown of the numbers, and links to other resources.
Link to presentation
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Series Group Forecasting with R and Interactive Visualization with ggvis - Roy Budhaditya</title>
      <link>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/09/18/sep2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/09/18/sep2018/</guid>
      <description>Abstract We will be discussing time series group forecasting in R as well as ggvis visualization. Forecasting is always a topic of importance with the availability of several models such as ARIMA, seasonal decomposition, exponential smoothing and so on. Each and every method produces different or close to similar output based on the data we use. We will be going through a hands on forecast modelling in R using Tidyverse and MAPA package.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Story Mapping with igraph - Bill McLellan</title>
      <link>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/08/21/aug2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/08/21/aug2018/</guid>
      <description>Abstract This talk will illustrate how to script a particular R solution for graph analysis to forecast scrum and kanban project cycle time given story links, points and team velocities. This will be followed by brainstorm with the group on how to start generalizing the solution for a project analysis package
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Databases from R - Alex Axthelm</title>
      <link>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/07/19/jul2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/07/19/jul2018/</guid>
      <description>The abstract of the talk and link to presented material are below.
Abstract Alex gave a demo of how to use R code to access and process data form SQL server.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neural Networks in R with nnet package - Harry Rowe</title>
      <link>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/06/19/jun2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/06/19/jun2018/</guid>
      <description>The abstract of the talk and link to presented material are below.
Abstract This talk will cover a simple example of neural network using nnet package. The talk would show example of continuous output and classifier (using iris dataset) and show tuning of classifier with repeated cross validation.
Link to material from talk
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning Your Analysis into an API with Plumber - Derrick Kearney</title>
      <link>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/05/15/may2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/05/15/may2018/</guid>
      <description>Derrick covered the topic of turning Analysis into an API with Plumber. The abstract of the talk and link to presented material are below.
Abstract You’ve imported the data, cleaned it up, and built the model. Your next step is to communicate your findings with others. Typically this would mean writing a report or building a web application so other people could visualize how the model works, but sometime your Communicate step is someone else’s Import step.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using R in Power BI - Ryan Wade</title>
      <link>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/04/17/apr2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/04/17/apr2018/</guid>
      <description>Ryan wade covered the topic of using R in Power BI. The abstract of the talk, Ryan’s profile and link to presented material are below.
Abstract R is a very powerful statistical programming language that has been gaining a lot of traction in recent years. In early 2015 Microsoft acquired Revolution Analytics, a major provider of software and services for R. Microsoft have since incorporated R in Azure ML, SQL Server 2016, and Power BI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to Reticulate Package - Shankar</title>
      <link>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/03/20/mar2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/03/20/mar2018/</guid>
      <description>Shankar covered the basics of reticulate package. The codes covered in the talk are in this location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rstudio::conf2018 and tidyeval Discussion - Will Landau</title>
      <link>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/02/20/feb2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/02/20/feb2018/</guid>
      <description>Will talked about rstudio::conf2018 and discussed tidyeval concepts that he recently learnt at Hadley Wickham’s rstudio::conf2018 tutorial. (link to Will’s presentation material)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discussion of 2018 plans</title>
      <link>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/01/16/jan2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/01/16/jan2018/</guid>
      <description>We discussed plans for 2018 as a group. Below are notes from the discussion
Ideas on content to cover in the meetups  trivia short package intro and go through vignette with some extensions go through datasets from different industries
 people can ask questions (ask a few days before) so that they can be addressed during the meetup
 Topics of interest:  github docker/rocker setting up RStudio/Shiny in cloud (AWS, google cloud etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>