<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A Hugo website</title>
    <link>/IndyUserWebpg/</link>
    <description>Recent content on A Hugo website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/IndyUserWebpg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to Reticulate Package - Shankar</title>
      <link>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/03/20/mar2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/03/20/mar2018/</guid>
      <description>Shankar covered the basics of reticulate package. The codes covered in the talk are in this location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rstudio::conf2018 and tidyeval Discussion - Will Landau</title>
      <link>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/02/20/feb2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/02/20/feb2018/</guid>
      <description>Will talked about rstudio::conf2018 and discussed tidyeval concepts that he recently learnt at Hadley Wickham’s rstudio::conf2018 tutorial. (link to Will’s presentation material)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discussion of 2018 plans</title>
      <link>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/01/16/jan2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/IndyUserWebpg/2018/01/16/jan2018/</guid>
      <description>We discussed plans for 2018 as a group. Below are notes from the discussion
Ideas on content to cover in the meetups  trivia short package intro and go through vignette with some extensions go through datasets from different industries
 people can ask questions (ask a few days before) so that they can be addressed during the meetup
 Topics of interest:  github docker/rocker setting up RStudio/Shiny in cloud (AWS, google cloud etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/IndyUserWebpg/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/IndyUserWebpg/about/</guid>
      <description>The IndyUseR Group is dedicated to bringing together users of R (at all levels of experience from beginner to expert level) to exchange knowledge, inspire new users, and spur the adoption of R for innovative research and commercial applications.
The meetup page for IndyUseR group is at this location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/IndyUserWebpg/prevyearsmeetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/IndyUserWebpg/prevyearsmeetings/</guid>
      <description>2017 Meetings  November 2017: Perspective on Base R and Tidyverse by Stephen October 2017: An R Text Mining Case Study - Harry Rowe September 2017: Exploring UN General Debates Kaggle Dataset with R NLP Tools August 2017: Reproducibility and high-performance computing with drake July 2017: R in the development and analysis of forensic credibility assessment tests June 2017: Exploring Simmer - An R Package for Discrete Event Simulation May 2017: Overview of Julia by a R User April 2017: Cybersecurity Discussion March 2017: FREDcast, R Trivia, General Discussion February 2017: FREDcast, R Trivia, Webscraping and htmlWidgets January 2017: Kickoff Meeting for Year, General Discussion, Trends in Statistical Papers Using Google Scholar - Matt Gillam   2016 Meetings  November 2016: Predicting NBA Games using SQL R Services - Ryan Wade October 2016: New R tools for workflow management, testing, and reproducibility - Will Landau September 2016: Intro to R Programming at IUPUI - Fred Kukral August 2016: Presentation about feather - Matt Gillam July 2016: UseR 2016 Recap - Adam Simkowski June 2016: Leveraging Weather Data in R - Adam Simkowski May 2016: Big Molecules Meets Big Data: Predicting Protein Tertiary Structure from Combinatorial Chemistry Data - Stan Siranovich April 2016: Using R and Power BI to Analyze US Trade Balance with Other Countries - Ryan Wade March 2016: System Configuration and Development of R in Jupyter Notebook February 2016: Book overview: Mastering Machine Learning with R - Cory Lesmeister January 2016: Webscraping with rvest package - Shankar Vaidyaraman   2015 Meetings  November 2015: Typical Excel Tasks in R - Stuart Ward, Demo of a Shiny App that Analyzes Sentiments and Produces Wordcloud of Sentiments - J.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>